Finding Aid for the Republic Pictures Corporation Records LSC.0979
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Continuity Scripts
  - Zansabaku., 1955.; 15 copies. (Box 27)
    Director: Lewis Cotlow (prod.)
    Cast: Documentary Feature
  - Zansabuku. CUT, 1955.; 1 copy. (Box 27)
    Director: Lewis Cotlow (P)
  - A Thousand Dollars a Minute., 5 copies. (Box 27)
    Cast: Roger Pryor
  - Thoroughbreds. CUT, 5 copies. (Box 27)
    Cast: Tom Neal Adele Mara
    - Thoroughbreds (trailer)., 19 copies.
  - Thoroughbreds., 1944.; 7 copies. (Box 27)
    Cast: Tom Neal, Adele Mara
  - The Sun Shines Bright., 1953.; 18 copies. (Box 27)
    Cast: Charles Winninger, Arleen Whelan
  - Hell's Outpost., 1954.; 10 copies. (Box 27)
    Cast: Rod Cameron, Joan Leslie
  - Hell's Outpost. CUT, 1954.; 5 copies. (Box 27)
    Cast: Rod Cameron, Joan Leslie, Chill Wills, John Russell, Jim Davis
  - The Road to Denver., 1955.; 9 copies. (Box 28)
    Cast: John Payne, Mona Freeman, Lee J. Cobb, Ray Middleton
  - Santa Fe Saddlemates., 1945.; 11 copies. (Box 28)
  - Song of Mexico., 1945.; 10 copies. (Box 28)
  - Plainsman and the Lady., 1946.; 12 copies. (Box 28)
    Cast: William Elliott, Vera Ralston
  - Man from Rainbow Valley., 1946.; 20 copies. (Box 28)
    Director: Robert Springsteen
    Cast: Monte Hale, Adrian Booth, Jo Ann Marlowe, Ferris Taylor
  - The Man from the Rio Grande., 1943.; 5 copies. (Box 28)
    Cast: Don RED Barry, Wally Vernon, TWINKLE WATTS
  - Gun Lords of Stirrup Basin., 5 copies. (Box 28)
    Cast: Bob Steele, Louise Stanley, Karl Hackett
  - Gun Lords of Stirrup Basin. CUT, 7 copies. (Box 28)
    Cast: Bob Steele, Louise Stanley
  - Desperadoes of Dodge City., 1948.; 18 copies. (Box 28)
    Cast: Allan Rocky Lane
  - Desperadoes of Dodge City. CUT, 1948.; 10 copies. (Box 28)
    Cast: Allan 'Rocky' Lane, Eddy Waller
  - Outlaws of Santa Fe., 1944.; 10 copies. (Box 28)
    Cast: Don Barry, Helen Talbot, Wally Bernon, Twinkle Watts!
  - Outlaws of Santa Fe. CUT, 1944.; 5 copies. (Box 28)
    Cast: Don Red Barry, Helen Talbot, Wally Vernon, Twinkle Watts
  - Pistol Packin' Mama., 1943.; 7 copies. (Box 28)
    Director: Frank Woodruff
    Cast: Ruth Terry, Robert Livingston, Wally Vernon
  - The Lonely Trail., 1937.; 1 copy. (Box 28)
    Cast: John Wayne, Ann Rutherford, Cy Kendall
  - Lone Star Raiders., 1940.; 10 copies. (Box 28)
  - Lone Star Raiders. CUT, 1940.; 7 copies. (Box 28)
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Bob Steele, R Ruff Davis
  - Iron Mountain Trail., 1953.; 10 copies. (Box 28)
  - The Chicago Kid., 1945.; 10 copies. (Box 29)
    Cast: Donald Barry, Otto Kruger, Lynne Roberts, Henry Daniels
  - Grissly's Millions., 1944.; 6 copies. (Box 29)
    Cast: Paul Kelly, Virginia Grey, Paul Fix, Byron Foulger
  - I Cover the Underworld., 1955.; 10 copies. (Box 29)
    Cast: Sean McClory, Joanne Jordan
  - I Cover the Underworld. CUT, 1955.; 1 copy. (Box 46)
    Cast: Sean McClory, Joanne Jordan, Ray Middleton, Jaclynne Green
  - Jaguar., 1955.; 5 copies. (Box 29)
    Cast: Sabu, Chiquita, Barton MacLane
    - Jaguar. (trailer)., 1955; 9 copies.
    - Jaguar. (Superimposed Spotted List - English copy)., 1955; 4 copies.
    - Jaguar. (Spanish dialog translation for feature and trailer)., 1955; 3 copies.
    - Jaguar. (Portuguese dialect translation for feature and trailer)., 1955; 4 copies.
  - Jaguar. CUT, (1955).; 2 copies. (Box 29)
    Cast: Asbu, Chiquita, Marton MacLane
  - Lost Planet Airmen., 1949.; 4 copies. (Box 29)
    Director: Fred. c. Brannon
    Cast: Tristram Coffin, Mae Clarke, Don Haggerty
    - Trailer., 24 copies.
  - Love, Honor and Goodbye., 1945.; 2 copies. (Box 29)
    Cast: Virginia Bruce, Edward Ashley, Victor McLaglen, Nils Asther
  - Love, Honor and Goodbye. CUT, 1945.; 1 copy. (Box -)
    Cast: Virginia Bruce, Edward Ashley, Victor McLaglen
  - The Pittsburgh Kid., 1941.; 4 copies. (Box 29)
    Director: Jack Townley
    Cast: Jean Parker, Dick Purcell
  - Sands of Iwo Jima., 1949.; 5 copies. (Box 29)
    Cast: John Wayne, John Agar, Forrest Tucker, Adele Mara
  - Sands of Iwo Jima. (trailer). CUT, 1949; 21 copies. (Box 29)
  - Scotland Yard Investigator., 1945.; 9 copies. (Box 29)
    Cast: Sir Aubrey Smith, Erich Von Stroheim
  - A Scream in the Dark., 1943.; 5 copies. (Box 29)
    Cast: Robert Lowery, Marie McDonald
  - Sweethearts on Parade., 1 copy. (Box 29)
    Cast: Ray Middleton, Lucillo Norman
    - Sweethoarts on Parade (trailer)., 1953.; 19 copies.
  - Trent's Last Case., 1952.; 10 copies. (Box 29)
    Cast: Michael Wilding, Margaret Lockwood, Orsen Welles
  - The Castaway., 1945.; 10 copies. (Box 30)
    Cast: Joseph Schildkraut, Billie Burke, One Munson
  - The Castaway. CUT, 1945; 4 copies.
  - Who Killed Aunt Maggie?., 1940.; 3 copies. (Box 30)
    Cast: John Hubbard, Wendy Barrie, Edgar Kennedy
  - Secret Venture., 10 copies. (Box 30)
    Cast: Kent Taylor, Kathleen Byron
  - Change of Heart., 1943.; 10 copies. (Box 30)
    Cast: John Carroll, Susan Hayward
  - Hollywood Stadium Mystery., 10 copies. (Box 30)
    Director: David Howard
    Cast: Neil Hamilton, Evelyn Venable, Lucien Littlefield
  - A Song For Miss Julie., 1945.; 10 copies. (Box 30)
  - Trigger Trio., 1937.; 4 copies. (Box 30)
    Cast: Ray Corrigan, Max,Terhune
  - Steppin' in Society., 1945.; 4 copies. (Box 30)
  - Earl Carroll Vanities., 9 copies. (Box 30)
    Cast: Dennis O'Keefe, Constance Moore, Eve Arden
    - Earl Carroll Vanities. (trailer)., 17 copies.
  - Mama Runs Wild., 1938.; 10 copies. (Box 30)
    Cast: Mary Boland, Ernest Truex
  - Secrets of Scotland Yard., 1944.; 7 copies. (Box 30)
    Cast: Edgar Barrier, Stephanie Bachelor, C. Aubrey Smith, Lionel Atwell
  - Corporal Dolan Goes A.W.O.L.., 1946.; 10 copies. (Box 30)
    Cast: Eddie Albert, Faye Marlowe, Gail Patrick
  - Stranger at My Door., 1956.; 12 copies. (Box 31)
    Cast: MacDonald Carey, Patricia Medina, Skip Homeier
    - Stranger at My Door. (trailer)., 1956; 9 copies.
  - Shadows of Tombstone., 1953.; 5 copies. (Box 31)
    Cast: Rex Allen, Slim Pickesn
  - Sundown in Santa Fe., 1948.; 10 copies. (Box 31)
  - Sundown in Santa Fe. CUT, 1948.; 5 copies.
  - Ranger of Cherokee Strip., 1949.; 10 copies. (Box 31)
    Cast: Monte Hale, Paul Hurst, Alice Talton, Monte Blue
  - Silver City Kid., 1944.; 10 copies. (Box 31)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Peggy Steward
  - The San Antonio Kid., 1944.; 12 copies. (Box 31)
  - The San Antonio Kid. CUT, 1944.; 6 copies.
    General note
    dupe
    Cast: Wild Bill Elliott, Bobby Blake, Alice Fleming, Linda Stirling
  - Thunder in God's Country., 1951.; 9 copies. (Box 31)
    Cast: Rex Allen, Mary Ellen Kay, Buddy Ebsen
  - Captive of Billy the Kid., 1951.; 9 copies. (Box 31)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Penny Edwards, Grant Withers
  - The Last Musketeer., 1951.; 10 copies. (Box 31)
    Cast: Rex Allen, Rex, Mary Ellen Kay, Slim Pickens
  - Rustlers on Horseback., 1950.; 7 copies. (Box 31)
  - Johnny Ringo and Doc Holliday., 1954.; 10 copies. (Box 31)
    Cast: Jim Davis, Mary Castle, Donald Curtis
  - Sweethearts on Parade., 1953.; 5 copies. (Box 31)
    Cast: Ray Middleton, Lucille Norman
  - Night Riders of Montana., 1951.; 10 copies. (Box 31)
  - A Texan Rides., 13 copies. (Box 31)
    Cast: Bob Steele, Lois January
  - The Fabulous Texan., 1947.; 3 copies. (Box 31)
    Cast: William Elliott, John Carroll
  - Mr. District Attorney., 1941.; 10 copies. (Box 32)
    Cast: Dennis O'Keefe, Florence Rice, Peter Lorre
  - Mr. District Attorney. CUT, 1941.; 9 copies. (Box 32)
  - Dark Command., 1940.; 7 copies. (Box 32)
    Director: Raoul Walsh
    Cast: Claire Trevor, John Wayne
  - The West Side Kid., 1943.; 3 copies. (Box 32)
    Cast: Donald Barry, Henry Hull
  - Who Killed Aunt Maggie., 1940.; 4 copies. (Box 32)
    Cast: John Hubbard, Wendy Barrie
  - When Gangland Strikes., 1945.; 4 copies. (Box 32)
    Cast: Raymond Groenleaf, Marjie, Miller
    - When Gangland Strikes. (trailer)., 1945; 30 copies.
  - Tenth Avenue Kid., 1938.; 5 copies. (Box 32)
    Cast: Bruce Cabot, Beverly Roberts
  - A Desperate Adventure., 1938.; 15 copies. (Box 32)
    Cast: Ramon Navarro, Marian Marsh
  - The Big Gamble., 1948.; 10 copies. (Box 32)
    Cast: Marsha Hunt, William Lundigan, Charles Winninger
    - The Big Gamble. (trailer)., 1948; 55 copies.
  - The Kid from Cleveland., 1949.; 7 copies. (Box 32)
    Director: Herbert Kline
    Cast: George Brent, Lynn Bari Rusty Tamblyn
  - Tarnished., 1950.; 6 copies. (Box 32)
    Director: Harry Koller
    Cast: Dorothy Patrick, Arthur Franz
  - The Man Is Armed., 1956.; 8 copies. (Box 32)
    Cast: Dane Clark, William Talman
  - Ice-Capades Revue., 1942.; 7 copies. (Box 32)
    Cast: Ellen Drew, Richard Denning
  - Taming Sutton's Gal., 1957.; 12 copies. (Box 32)
    Cast: John Lupton, Gloria Talbott
    - Taming Sutton's Gal (trailer)., 1957.; 20 copies. (Box 32)
  - Riders of Whistling Skull., 1936.; 9 copies. (Box 33)
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Ray Corrigan, Max Terhune, Mary Russell
  - Surrender., 1950.; 4 copies. (Box 33)
    Cast: Vera Ralston, John Carroll, Walter Brennan, Jane Darwell
  - Rodeo King and the Señorita., 1951.; 10 copies. (Box 33)
    Cast: Rex Allen, Mary EllenKay, Buddy Ebsen
  - Tiburcio Vasquez and Black Bart (Stories of the Century)., 1954.; 10 copies. (Box 33)
    Cast: Jim Davis, Mary Castle, Anthony Caruso
  - Down Laredo Way., 1953.; 10 copies. (Box 33)
    Cast: Rex Allen, Slim Pickens, Dona Drake, Marjorie Lord
  - Lawless Land., 7 copies. (Box 33)
    Director: A.W. Hackel - prod.
    Cast: Johnny Mack Brown, Louise Stanley, Ted Adams
  - Lawless Land. CUT, 5 copies. (Box 33)
    Director: A. W. Hackel (p)
  - Old Overland Trail., 10 copies. (Box 33)
    Cast: Rex Allen, Koko, Slim Pickens, Roy Barcroft
  - Old Overland Trail. CUT, 1953.; 10 copies.
    - Old Overland Trail. trailer., 1953; 11 copies.
  - Joaquin Murietta and Chief Crazy Horse (Stories of the Century)., 1954.; 10 copies. (Box 33)
  - Leadville Gunslinger. CUT, 1952.; 9 copies. (Box 33)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller, Grant Withers
    - Leadville Gunslinger. (trailers)., 1952; 25 copies.
  - Leadville Gunslinger., 1952.; 5 copies. (Box 33)
    Cast: Allan Lena, Eddy Waller, Grant Withers
  - Drumbeats Over Wyoming., 1946.; 10 copies. (Box 33)
  - Westward Ho., 1942.; 4 copies. (Box 33)
  - Winds of the Wasteland., 1936.; 4 copies. (Box 33)
    Cast: John Wayne, Phyliss Fraser
  - Wells Fargo Gunmaster., 1951.; 1 copy. (Box 33)
    Cast: Allan Rooky Lane and his horse Black Jack
  - Death Valley Manhunt., 1943.; 6 copies. (Box 33)
    Cast: Wild Bill Elliott, George Hayes
  - Public Cowboy No. 1., 1937.; 6 copies. (Box 33)
    Cast: Gene Autry, Smiley Burnette
  - Santa Fe Passage. CUT, 1950.; 8 copies. (Box 33)
    Cast: John Payne, Faith Domergue, Rod Cameron, Slim Pickens
    - Santa Fe Passage. (trailer)., 1950; 28 copies.
  - Santa Fe Passage., 1955.; 2 copies. (Box 33)
  - The Congress Dances., 1955.; 10 copies. (Box 34)
  - Joan of Ozark., 1942.; 7 copies. (Box 34)
    Cast: Judy Canova, Joe. E. Brown
  - Jaguar., 1955.; 10 copies. (Box 34)
    Cast: Sabu, Chiquita, Barton MacLane, J
  - The Main Street Kid., 1947.; 2 copies. (Box 34)
    Cast: Janet Martin Alan Mowbray
    - The Main Street Kid. (trailer)., 1947; 2 copies.
  - A Man Alone., 1955.; 5 copies. (Box 34)
    Director: Ray Milland
    Cast: Ray Milland, Ward Bond, Mary Murphy, Raymond Burr
    - A Man Alone. (trailer)., 1955; 10 copies.
    - A Man Alone. (Superimposed Spotted List - English copy)., 1955; 3 copies.
    - A Man Alone. (Spanish dialog trans. for feature and trailer)., 1955; 4 copies.
    - A Man Alone. (Portuguese dialog trans. for feature and trailer)., 1955; 2 copies.
  - A Man Alone. CUT, 5 copies. (Box 34)
    Director: R. Milland
    Cast: Ray Milland, Mary Murphy, Ward Bond, Raymond Burr
    - trailer., 1955; 20 copies.
  - Faces in the Fog., 1944.; 10 copies. (Box 34)
    Cast: Jane Withers, Paul Kelly
  - Daughter of the Jungle., 1948.; 3 copies. (Box 34)
    Cast: Lois Hall, James Gardwell, William Wright
  - Jamboree., 1944.; 3 copies. (Box 34)
    Cast: Ruth Terry, George Byron
  - House of a Thousand Candles., 1936.; 3 copies. (Box 34)
    Cast: Phillips Holmes, Mae Clarke
  - Lisbon., 1956.; 10 copies. (Box 34)
    Cast: Ray Milland, Maureen O'Hara, Claude Rains, Yxonne Furneaux
  - Lisbon. CUT, 1956.; 2 copies. (Box 34)
    Cast: Ray Milland, Maureen O'Hara, Claude Rains
    - Lisbon. (trailer)., 1956; 4 copies.
    - Lisbon. (Superimposed Spotted List - English copy)., 1956; 2 copies.
    - Lisbon. (Portuguese dialect translation)., 1956; 1 copy.
    - Lisbon. (Spanish dialect translation for feature and trailer)., 1956; 1 copy.
  - Cross Channel. CUT, 10 copies. (Box 34)
    Cast: Wayne Morris, Yvonne Furneaux
  - Cross Channel., 1955.; 6 copies. (Box 34)
  - Untamed Heiress., 1954.; 10 copies. (Box 35)
    Director: Charles LeMont
    Cast: Judy Canova, Donald Barry, Jack Kruschen
  - Main Street Lawyer., 1939.; 2 copies. (Box 35)
    Director: Dudley Murphy
    Cast: Edward Ellis, Anita Louise, Margaret Hamilton
  - Hoodlum Empire., 1952.; 10 copies. (Box 35)
    Cast: Brian Donlevy, Claire Trevor, Forrest Tucker, Vera Ralston
  - Hoodlum Empire. (CUT)., 1952; 10 copies.
  - Duke of Chicago., 194?.; 10 copies. (Box 35)
    Cast: Tom Brown, Audrey Long, Grant Withers, Paul Harvey
  - Champ for a Day., 1953.; 7 copies. (Box 35)
    Cast: Alex Nicol, Audrey Totter, Charles Winninger, Henry Morgan
  - Champ for a Day. (CUT)., 1953; 10 copies.
  - The Cheaters., 1945.; 5 copies. (Box 35)
    Cast: Joseph Schildkraut, Billie Burke, Ona Munson
  - Grandpa Goes to Town., 1940.; 10 copies. (Box 35)
    Cast: James Gleason, Lucile Gleason, Russell Gleason, Harry Davenport, Maxie Rosenbloom!
  - Grandpa Goes To Town. CUT, 1940.; 5 copies. (Box 35)
    Cast: James Gleason, Lucile Gleason, Russell Gleason, Harry Davenport
  - The Lawless Eighties., 1957.; 8+16 copies. (Box 35)
  - Lightnin' In the Forest., 3 copies. (Box 35)
    Cast: Lynne Roberts, Donald Barry, Warren Douglas
    - trailer., 1948; 26 copies.
  - Night Train to Memphis., 1946.; 10 copies. (Box 35)
    Cast: Roy Acuff, Allan Lane, Adele Mara, Irving Bacon
  - Hell's Half Acre., 1954.; 10 copies. (Box 35)
    Cast: Wendell Corey, Evelyn Keyes, Elsa Lanchester, Marie Windsor
  - Yellowneck., 1954.; 10 copies. (Box 35)
    Director: R. John Hugh
    Cast: Lin McCarthy, Stephen Courtleigh, Berry Kroeger, Bill Mason
  - A Perilous Journey., 1953.; 10 copies. (Box 35)
    Cast: Vera Ralston, David Brian
  - MacBeth., 1 copy. (Box 35)
    Director: Orson Welles
    Cast: Orson Welles
  - King of the Race Track., 1947.; 10 copies. (Box 35)
    Cast: Don Ameche, Catherine McLeod, Roscoe Karns
  - Don Juan's Night of Love., 1952.; 10 copies. (Box 36)
    Director: Mario Soldati
    Cast: Raf Vallone, Silvana Pampaninil, Michele Philippe
    - Don Juan's Night of Love. (trailer)., 1952; 21 copies.
  - Don Juan's Night of Love. CUT, 1952.; 3 copies. (Box *)
    Cast: Raf Vallone, Silvana Pampanini, Michele Philippe, Jacques Castelot
    - Don Juan's Night of Love. (trailer)., 1952; [Duplicate].; 5 copies.
  - Prisoners in Petticoats., 1950.; 3 copies. (Box 36)
    Cast: Valentine Perkins, Robert Rockwell, Marlo Dwyer
    - Trailer., 10 copies.
  - Oklahoma Annie., 1951.; 10 copies. (Box 36)
    Cast: Judy Canova, John Russell, Grant Withers, Minerva Urecal!
  - Oklahoma Annie. CUT, 1951; 16 copies.
  - The Main Street Kid., 1947.; 4 copies. (Box 36)
    Cast: Al Pearce, Janet Martin
  - Manhattan Merry-go-round., 1937.; 6 copies. (Box 36)
    Cast: Ann Dvorak, Tamara Geva, James Gleason, Ted Lewis
  - Duke of Chicago., 1949.; 3 copies. (Box 36)
    Cast: Tom Brown, Audrey Long, Grant Withers
  - False Faces., 1943.; 3 copies. (Box 36)
    Cast: Stanley Ridges, Bill Henry, Rex Williams, Beda Ann Borg
  - The Phantom Speaks., 1945.; 3 copies. (Box 36)
    Cast: Richard Arlenn, Stanley Ridges
  - Federal Agent At Large., 1950.; 5 copies. (Box 36)
    Cast: Dorothy Patrick, Robert Rockwell, Kent Taylor, Estelita Rodriguez
  - Faces In the Fog., 1944.; 5 copies. (Box 36)
    Cast: Jane Withers, Paul Kolly, Lee Patrick
  - Goodnight, Sweetheart., 1944.; 10 copies. (Box 36)
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Ruth Terry, Chester Conklin
  - Goodnight, Sweetheart. CUT, 1944.; 4 copies. (Box 36)
    Cast: Robert Livingston, Ruth Terry, Henry Hull, Chester Cinklin
  - The Divided Heart., 1954.; 10 copies. (Box 36)
    Cast: Cornell Borchers, Yvonne Mitchell, Armin Dallen, Alexander Knox
  - The Purple V., 1943.; 2 copies. (Box 36)
    Cast: John Archer, Mary McLeod
  - This Is Korea., 3 copies. (Box 36)
    Director: Herbert J. Yates, (p)
  - Zorro Rides Again., 1937.; 16 copies. (Box 37)
    Director: William Entney, John English
    Cast: Mona Rico, Tom London
  - West of Cimarron., 1942.; 3 copies. (Box 37)
  - O, My Darling Clementine., 1943.; 1 copy. (Box 37)
    Cast: Roy Acuff and his Smoky Mountain Boys and Girls, Isabel Randolph
  - Navajo Trail Raiders., 1949.; 14 copies. (Box 37)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller, Robert Emmett Keane, Barbara Bestar
    - Navajo Trail Raiders. (trailor)., 1949; 9 copies.
  - Marshal of Amarillo., 1948.; 11 copies. (Box 37)
  - Marshal of Amarillo. (CUT)., 1948; 4 copies.
  - Out California Way., 1946.; 13 copies. (Box 37)
    Cast: Monte Hale, Adrian Booth, Bobby Blake
  - Duel At Apache Wells., 1957.; 7 copies. (Box 37)
    Cast: Anna Maria Alberghetti, Ben Cooper, Jim Davis, Harry Shannon
  - Raiders of the Range., 1942.; 4 copies. (Box 37)
    Cast: Bob Steele, Tom Tyler, Rufe Davis, Lois Collier
  - Range Defenders., 1937.; 7 copies. (Box 37)
  - Ranger of Cherokee Strip., 1949.; 5 copies. (Box 37)
    Cast: Monte Hale, Paul Hurst, Alice Talton, Monta Blue
    - Ranger of Cherokee Strip. (trailer)., 1949; 8 copies.
  - Man from Thunder River., 1943.; 3 copies. (Box 37)
    Cast: Wild Bill Elliott, Gabby Hayes, Anne Jeffreys, Ian Keith
  - Outlaws of Pine Ridge., 1942.; 1 copy. (Box 37)
    Cast: Don Red Barry, Lynn Merrick, Noah Boery, Donald Kirke
  - Outlaws of Pine Ridge. CUT, 1942.; 9 copies. (Box 31)
    Cast: Lynn Merrick, Noah Beery, Donald Kirke, Emmett Lynn
  - Outcasts of the Trail., 1949.; 2 copies. (Box 37)
    Cast: Monte Hale, Paul Hurst, Jeff Donnell, Minerva Urecal
  - Outcasts of the Trail. CUT, 1949.; 18 copies. (Box 31)
    Cast: Monte Hale, Paul Hurst, Jeff Donnell, Minerva Urecal!
    - Outcasts of the Trail. (Trailer)., 1949; 9 copies.
  - Night Train to Memphis., 1946.; 4 copies. (Box 37)
    Cast: Roy Acuff and His Smoky Mountain Boys, Allan Lane, Adele Mara
  - Night Raiders of Montana., 1951.; 5 copies. (Box 37)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Chubby Johnson, Roy Barcroft, Claudia Barrett
    - Night Raiders of Montana. (trailer)., 1951; 21 copies.
  - Invisible Enemy., 1938.; 2 copies. (Box 38)
    Cast: Alan Marshal, Tala Birell, Nady Correll
  - Invisible Avenger. CUT, 6 copies. (Box 38)
  - Invisible Avenger., 1959.; 11 copies. (Box 38)
    Director: James Wong Howe, John Sledge
    Cast: Richard Derr, Mark Daniels
  - I Dream of Jeanie., 1952.; 1 copy. (Box 38)
    Cast: Ray Middleton, Bill Shirley, Muriel Lawrence
  - Inside The Underworld., 1944.; 1 copy. (Box 38)
    Cast: Erich Von Stroheim, Vera Ralston, Richard Arlen
  - Insurance Investigator., 1951.; 4 copies. (Box 38)
    Cast: Richard Dening, Audrey Long, John Eldredge
  - Dark Command., 1940.; 6 copies. (Box 38)
    Cast: Claire Trevor, John Wayne, Walter Pidgeon, Roy Rogers, George Hayes, Marjorie Main
  - My Wife's Relatives., 1939.; 7 copies. (Box 38)
    Cast: James Gleason, Lucile Gleason
  - Post Office Investigator., 1949.; 14 copies. (Box 38)
    Cast: Audrey Long, Warren Douglas
    - (Trailer)., 7 copies.
  - Meet the Stars., 1940.; 5 copies. (Box 38)
    Director: _____
    Cast: Harriet Parsons and Various stars
  - Man of Conquest., 1939.; 11 copies. (Box 38)
    Cast: Richard Dix, Gail Patrick, Edward Ellis, Joan Fontaine
  - Mercy Island., 1941.; 1 copy. (Box 38)
    Cast: Ray Middleton, Gloria Dickson
  - Passkey To Danger., 1946.; [Duplicate]; 21 copies. (Box 38)
    Cast: Kane Richmond, Stephanie Bachelor
  - Passkey to Danger. CUT, 1946.; 4 copies. (Box 38)
    Cast: Kane Richmond, Stephanie Bachelor, Adele Mara, Gregory Gay
  - The Night Hawk., 1938.; 3 copies. (Box 38)
    Cast: Robert Livingston, June Travis, Robert Armstrong, Ben Welden
  - Brimstone., 1949.; 2 copies. (Box 39)
    Cast: Rod Cameron, Adrian Booth Walter Brennan, Forrest Tucker
  - Dakota., 1945.; 2 copies. (Box 39)
    Cast: John Wayne, Vera Ralston, Walter Brennan, Ward Bond, Ona Munson
    - Dakota. (trailer)., 1945; 4 copies.
  - Rough Riders of Durange. CUT, 1951.; 12 copies. (Box 39)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Walter Baldwin, Aline Towne, Steve Darrell
    - Rough Riders of Durange. (trailer)., 1951; 21 copies.
  - Rough Riders of Durango., 1951.; 2 copies. (Box 39)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Walter Baldwin, Aline Towne
  - Daniel Boone, Trail Blazer., 1956.; 4 copies. (Box 39)
    Cast: Bruce Bennett, Lon Chaney, Faron Young, Kem Dibbs
    - Daniel Boone, Trail Blazer. (trailer)., 1956; 21 copies.
  - Under Mexicali Stars., 1950.; 12 copies. (Box 39)
    Cast: Rex Allen, Dorothy Patrick, Roy Barcroft, Buddy Ebsen
  - Under Mexicali Stars. (CUT)., 1950; 1 copy. (Box 39)
  - FireBrands of Arizona., 1944.; 9 copies. (Box 39)
    Cast: Sunset Carosn, Smiley Burnette, Peggy Stewart, Earle Hodgins
  - Wyoming., 1947.; 3 copies. (Box 39)
    Cast: William Elliott, Vera Ralston, John Carroll, George Hayes Gabby
  - The Wyoming Bandit., 1949.; 3 copies. (Box 39)
  - The Wyoming Bandit. CUT, 1949.; 10 copies. (Box 39)
  - Sheriff of Wichita., 1949.; 1 copy. (Box 39)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller, Roy Barcroft, Lyn Wilde
  - Flame of Sacramento., 1946.; 7 copies. (Box 39)
    Cast: William Elliott, Constance Moore
  - Flame of Sacramento. CUT, 1946.; [Duplicate].; 4 copies.
    Cast: William Elliott, Constance Moore, Hank Daniels, Ruth Donnelly
  - Phantom Stallion., 1954.; 4 copies. (Box 39)
  - Homesteaders of Paradise Valley., 6 copies. (Box 39)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Martha Wentworth, Ann Todd, Gene Stutenroth
  - Wells Fargo Gunmaster., 1951.; 10 copies. (Box 39)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Chubby Johnson, Mary Ellen Kay
  - El Paso Stampede., 1953.; 9 copies. (Box 39)
    Cast: Allan Lane, Eddy Waller, Phyllis Coates, Stephan Chase
    - El Paso Stampede. (trailer)., 1953; 18 copies.
  - Secret Venture., 7 copies. (Box 40)
    Cast: Kent Taylor, Kathleen Byron, Jane Hylton, Karel Stepanek
    - Trailer., 10 copies.
    - [Spotted trailer]., 3 copies.
    - [Port. trailer]., 1 copy.
  - Sons of Adventure., 1948.; 7 copies. (Box 40)
    Cast: Lynne Roberts, Russ Hayden, Gordon Jones
    - Sons of Adventure. (trailer)., 1948; 5 copies.
  - Sis Hopkins., 1941.; 8 copies. (Box 40)
    Cast: Judy Canova, Bob Crosby, Charles Butterworth
  - End of the Road., 1944.; 4 copies. (Box 40)
    Cast: Edward Norris, John Abbott, June Storey, Jonathan Hale
  - The Flame., 1947.; 10 copies. (Box 40)
    Cast: John Carroll, Vera Ralston, Robert Paige, Broderick Crowford
  - The Red Pony. (Steinbeck)., 1948; 14 copies [2 copies]. (Box 40)
    Director: Lewis Milestone
    Cast: Myna Loy, Robert Mitchum, Louis Calhern, Shepperd Strudwick
  - The Wayward Girl., 1957.; 5 copies. (Box 40)
    Cast: Marcia Henderson, Peter Walker Katharine Barrett, Whit Bissell
  - The Pilgrim Lady., 1946.; 19 copies. (Box 40)
    Director: Leslie Selander
  - Flaming Fury., 1949.; 11 copies. (Box 40)
    Cast: Roy Roberts, George Cooper, David Wolfe, Billy Wayne
  - Flame of Youth., 1949.; 7 copies. (Box 40)
    Cast: Barbra Fuller, Ray McDonald, Danni Nolan, Tony Barrett
  - Joyride., 10 copies. (Box 40)
    Cast: Gene Evans, Scott Marlowe, Carolyn Kearney, Robert Arthur
  - Satan's Satellites., 1952.; 2 copies. (Box 40)
    Director: Fred D. Brannon